恶魔城
第四季 第１集
‎六周前
情况真是糟糕透了
This could not have gone more wrong.
‎到底是怎么了
What happened?
‎我们花了几个月的时间过你的生活
We've spent a couple of months living your life.
‎充满冒险和胜利
Adventures and victories.
‎现在...
And now...
‎该过我的生活了
we're living my life.
‎五周前
‎下次 ‎找个不那么危险的地方撒尿 好吗
Next time, find somewhere less dangerous to pee, huh?
‎好吧
Yeah.
‎‎四周前
‎这不是我的错
This isn't my fault.
‎很公平 这次是我的错
Quite fair. This one's on me.
‎-我会弥补过失的  -‎靠你自己吗
- I will make it right. - On your own?
‎我们寡不敌众 ‎他们比我们高大
We're outnumbered, they're bigger than us,
看上去怒气冲冲的
and they look quite annoyed.
‎你最好蹲下来
You may want to crouch.
‎你瞧
Look.
他们从哪弄来的这个
Where did they get that?
‎也许出自布勒伊拉的城堡
Perhaps it washed out of the castle at Braila.
‎难怪这些家伙这么生气
No wonder these creatures were so angry.
‎我们打扰了他们的祈祷
We disturbed them while they were praying to it.
‎‎‎三周前
‎这是魔咒
It's a spell.
-‎依靠杀人来唤醒  -‎什么魔咒
- Murder wakes it up. - What kind of spell?
‎起死回生
Resurrection.
这办法根本没用 ‎少了东西
It wouldn't have worked. It's missing parts.
‎但他原本要杀了这些人来试手
But he would have killed these people to try.
-‎少了什么东西  -一道‎印记 ‎算是一种神奇的密码
- And the other thing? - A sigil. Sort of a magical code.
‎上面会有他
It will have the name of the person
想要复活的人的名字
he was trying to bring back from the dead.
‎让我猜猜看
Oh, let me guess.
‎破译出来就是弗拉德·德古拉·特佩斯
It decodes as Vlad Dracula Tepes.
‎为什么有人会这样做
Why the fuck would anyone do that?
‎你们会这样做吗
Would you do that?
‎没错
Oh, exactly.
天啊 我真是快疯了
God, this is getting on my nerves.
真希望我能杀你两次
I wish I could fucking kill you twice!
‎‎两周前
‎妈的
Shit!
-‎你刚刚说什么  -‎我说"妈的" 不行吗
- What did you just say? - I said, "shit," okay?
‎行啊 只是你从来不骂人
Yes, it's just that you never, you know, curse.
‎我从来没骂过人 后来发生了这些事
I never used to, and then all this happened.
然后遇到了你
And then you happened.
‎‎-我吗  -没错 就是你
- Me? - Yes, you.
‎我本来很有礼貌
I was nice.
‎然后我遇到了你 现在我像你一样
And then I met you, and now I'm like you.
所以 是我的错吗
Oh, so it's my fault.
‎都是你的错
It's all your fault!
‎你把我变成了这样
You did this to me!
‎我发现你他妈在坟墓里变成了雕像
I found you turned into a statue in a fucking tomb!
‎然后你缠上我
And climbed all over me,
‎从那一刻起 一切都糟透了 ‎而且…
and since that moment everything has been shit and...
‎我他妈的在说话呢
I am fucking talking here!
‎你让我学会了骂人
And you turned me into someone who says "shit."
‎去你妈的傻逼大混球
Fuckity shit hairy arse-warts giant slimy balls!
‎妈的
Shit!
‎‎‎一周前
‎活人献祭真的死灰复燃了
Human sacrifice really is back in fashion.
‎这又是为了德古拉伯爵吗
Do we think this is about Dracula again?
‎我觉得 这些人只不过在发疯
I think these people are just out of their minds.
‎所以我们不会试着跟他们讲道理
And so we're not going to try and reason with them.
‎不
No!
‎他们要杀害孩子
They were going to murder children.
‎孩子们 趴下 快点
Kids, lay down flat. Now!
‎那是什么玩意
What's that thing?
‎我只在书上看过画像
I've only seen drawings in books.
‎他有很多名字
He has a lot of names.
‎他通常被称为镰刀死神
Most often, he's called the Grim Reaper.
或者就叫死神
Or just Death.
‎他真的是死神吗
He's actually Death?
‎我是说 死神就长这样吗
I mean, this is what Death looks like?
‎因为我希望更好看些
Because I was hoping for something nicer.
‎才不是呢
Nah.
‎只是远古时代的人
Just people from an earlier time
‎想弄清楚他们看到的景象
trying to understand what they were seeing.
‎有些元素生物只以自然界的东西为食
There are elemental beings that just feed on things in nature.
‎他不是死神 他只是吞噬死亡
He's not Death. He just eats death.
‎那你觉得这只是他的神殿吗
So this is just a shrine to him, you think?
‎人们仍然认为这是死神本人吗
People who still think this is Death itself?
‎人们来此朝拜
Paying tribute.
‎也许希望他能让德古拉伯爵起死回生
Maybe in the hope that he can give Dracula back to them.
‎别误会我的意思
Don't get me wrong.
他可以夺人性命
He's supposed to be lethal.
‎却没有深入地狱
But he's not the sort of power who can reach into Hell
让人复活的力量
and pull someone out.
‎全世界都疯了
The whole world's gone crazy.
‎这块大石头呢
And this big stone?
‎石板
Flagstone.
‎一定是从某个城镇广场上撬来的
Must have been prized up from a town square somewhere.
‎最近哪个地方的广场上有石板
What's the nearest place that would have flagstones in their square?
‎‎‎今晚
‎‎‎塔哥维斯特
‎真的越来越难对付了
This is getting harder.
‎真的吗
Really?
‎我没注意到
I hadn't noticed over the sound
‎全身的肌肉和骨头都在吱嘎作响
of all my muscles and bones screaming.
‎天啊
Oh, God.
‎你会活下去的
You'll live.
‎天啊 但愿如此
God, I hope so.
‎他们到底在这下面找什么呢
What were they even looking for down here?
‎他们不需要更多武器
They can't need more weapons.
‎这些东西
This stuff.
‎很多武器都有些年头了
A lot of it is a good deal older.
‎上面有魔力的气味
This stinks of magic.
‎他们在找工具
They were looking for tools.
‎要是我们没有跟丢他们
If we hadn't lost track of them,
‎这些人就不会死了
these people would all still be alive.
‎没错
Yeah.
这时候‎你应该说
This is where you're supposed to say
这不是我们的错 特雷弗
that it's not our fault, Trevor.
‎确实不是
It's not.
‎但经过六周的艰难历险 ‎如果我们没有累得要死
But if we weren't so tired after six weeks of this shit,
‎他们活下来的机会更大
they would have had a better chance.
天啊
Oh, God.
‎没错
Right.
我们得找个安全的地方睡觉
We need to find somewhere safe to sleep.
‎明天好好休息一下
And take tomorrow to rest
‎把这些事情想清楚
and think all this through.
‎我想不明白
I don't get it.
‎我们杀了德古拉伯爵
We killed Dracula.
‎现在 我们要用余生的时间
And now we have to spend the rest of our lives
‎确保没人能让他起死回生吗
making sure nobody brings him back from the dead?
‎这个结果我没法接受
This is not what I agreed to.
‎一切都始于这个地方 对吧
This is where it all started, isn't it?
塔哥维斯特
Targoviste.
‎那个杂种戴着贝尔蒙特的纹章吗
Is that bastard wearing the Belmont crest?
戴了
He is.
‎他身边有一位传颂者魔法师
And that's a Speaker Magician with him.
‎斯拉德克和伊凡没有出来
And Sladek and Ivan didn't come out.
‎我知道 我看到了
I know that. I've got eyes.
‎这样不公平
This isn't fair.
‎我是德古拉伯爵的第一批忠实信徒
I was one of Dracula's first loyal followers.
‎他本来要把一切交给我
He was going to give me everything.
‎我差点就成功了
And I was close.
‎差点就能解决所有问题
So close to fixing it all.
‎但现在我必须面对 一个贝尔蒙特家族的人和一个疯狂的魔法师
But now I have to deal with a Belmont and a mad magician?!
‎-瓦尼 我们得走了  -‎去哪里
- Varney, we need to go. - Go where?
这里才是我应该待的地方
This is where I'm supposed to be.
‎战争开始时 ‎我来到这里占领塔哥维斯特
At the start of the war, I came here to take Targoviste
‎作为礼物献给德古拉伯爵
and give it to Dracula as a gift.
‎为什么大家这么难对付 ‎
Why is everyone making it so fucking hard?
‎-他们难道不知道我是谁吗  -不知道
- Don't they know who I am? - No.
‎我是瓦尼
I'm Varney.
‎伦敦的黑暗市长 英伦三岛的魔头
Night Mayor of London, Terror of the British Isles,
‎整个欧洲的吸血鬼之王
king vampire cocksman of all Europe.
‎我不需要忍受这种事
And I don't have to put up with this.
去吧
Go, go.
‎回巢穴去
Back to the nest.
‎我要把你们两个当做我他妈的晚餐
I'll have both of you for my fucking dinner.
‎我应该多喝水 少喝酒
I should drink more water and less wine.
‎伤口就会结痂愈合
This is coming out as scabs and wax.
"致城堡的阿鲁卡多"
"To the Alucard of the castle."
‎看在上帝的份上
For God's sake.
‎为什么我现在成阿鲁卡多了
Why I am the Alucard now?
"致城堡的阿鲁卡多
To the Alucard of the castle.
‎我们德内什蒂的人民求您伸出援手
We, the people of Danesti, beg your aid."
‎黑暗生物
Night creatures,
吸血鬼和可怕的恶魔袭击我们
vampires and terrible demons assault us,
‎我们不清楚原因
and we know not why.
‎我们防御薄弱 人数逐渐减少
Our defenses weaken and our numbers dwindle.
‎恳求您 先生 ‎拯救我们的灵魂”
Please, sir, save our souls."
‎拯救我们的灵魂
Save our souls.
‎那地方有32公里远
That's a good 20 miles away.
‎你可以闭嘴了
You can shut up.
‎而你一直坚持骑马
And you still kept on riding,
‎直到因疼痛或失血过多而死
until you died from the pain or the blood loss.
‎也许两种原因都有
Or both.
‎你就待在那里
You stay right there.
‎我跟你还没完呢
I'm not done with you yet.
‎少拉点屎 拜托
A bit less of your shit, please.
‎我的天啊
Oh, my God.
‎我要变成贝尔蒙特了
I'm turning into Belmont.